<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_mode_incompat_dialog_title">Cannot Open App</string>
    <string name="certificate_expiring_warning_title">Licence Expiring Soon</string>
    <string name="controllers_req_pt_portal_desc">Please use a controller to continue setting up a pass-through keyboard area.</string>
    <string name="guardian_acknowledge_quickboot_nux">OK</string>
    <string name="guardian_boundary_body_hand_imperial">Look down at the floor and hold your hand out in front of you. Pinch and hold your thumb and index finger together to draw along the boundary of your playing area. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We recommend a playing area size of 6.5 x 6.5 feet or greater for roomscale experiences.</string>
    <string name="guardian_boundary_body_hand_metric">Look down at the floor and hold your hand out in front of you. Pinch and hold your thumb and index finger together to draw along the boundary of your playing area. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We recommend a playing area size of 2 x 2 metres or greater for roomscale experiences.</string>
    <string name="guardian_boundary_body_imperial">Point your controller at the floor, then press and hold the trigger to draw along the boundary of your cleared playing area. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We recommend a playing area size of 6.5 x 6.5 feet or greater for roomscale experiences.</string>
    <string name="guardian_boundary_body_metric">Point your controller at the floor, then press and hold the trigger to draw along the boundary of your cleared playing area. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We recommend a playing area size of 2 x 2 metres or greater for roomscale experiences.</string>
    <string name="guardian_boundary_title">Define play area</string>
    <string name="guardian_confirm_couch_body">Make sure that the surface lines up with your sofa seat.</string>
    <string name="guardian_confirm_couch_guardian_body">Please confirm that you are entering the sofa space.</string>
    <string name="guardian_confirm_couch_title">Confirm Sofa</string>
    <string name="guardian_confirm_desk_body">Make sure that the surface lines up with your real desk.</string>
    <string name="guardian_confirm_desk_guardian_body">Make sure that the surface lines up with your real desk.</string>
    <string name="guardian_confirm_surface_editing_title">Customise MR Surfaces</string>
    <string name="guardian_confirm_whiteboard_body">Check to make sure that the virtual whiteboard plane matches up with your real whiteboard.</string>
    <string name="guardian_draw_couch_body_controller_imperial">&lt;p&gt;1. Hold your controller against the front edge of your sofa seat, then press and hold the trigger button.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;2. Draw a line from one side of the sofa to the other, then release the trigger button once you\'ve finished.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The minimum surface width is 12 inches.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Press B or Y to cancel.&lt;/p&gt;</string>
    <string name="guardian_draw_couch_body_controller_metric">&lt;p&gt;1. Hold your controller against the front edge of your sofa seat, then press and hold the trigger button.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;2. Draw a line from one side of the sofa to the other, then release the trigger button once you\'ve finished.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The minimum surface width is 30 cm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Press B or Y to cancel.&lt;/p&gt;</string>
    <string name="guardian_draw_couch_body_hand_imperial">&lt;p&gt;1. Hold your thumb and index finger against the front edge of your sofa seat, then pinch and hold both fingers together.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;2. Draw a line from one side of the sofa to the other, then release both fingers once you\'ve finished.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The minimum surface width is 12 inches.&lt;/p&gt;</string>
    <string name="guardian_draw_couch_body_hand_metric">&lt;p&gt;1. Hold your thumb and index finger against the front edge of your sofa seat, then pinch and hold both fingers together.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;2. Draw a line from one side of the sofa to the other, then release both fingers once you\'ve finished.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The minimum surface width is 30 cm.&lt;/p&gt;</string>
    <string name="guardian_draw_couch_title">Define Sofa Surface</string>
    <string name="guardian_draw_desk_body_controller_imperial">&lt;p&gt;1. Hold your controller on the front edge of your desk, then press and hold the trigger button.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;2. Draw a line from one side of the desk to the other, then release the trigger button when you\'ve finished.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The minimum surface width is 20 inches.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Press B or Y to cancel.&lt;/p&gt;</string>
    <string name="guardian_draw_desk_body_controller_metric">&lt;p&gt;1. Hold your controller on the front edge of your desk, then press and hold the trigger button.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;2. Draw a line from one side of the desk to the other, then release the trigger button when you\'ve finished.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The minimum surface width is 50 cm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Press B or Y to cancel.&lt;/p&gt;</string>
    <string name="guardian_draw_desk_body_hands_imperial">&lt;p&gt;1. Hold your thumb and index finger on the top front edge of your desk, then pinch and hold both fingers together.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;2. Draw a line from one side of the desk to the other, then open both fingers when you\'ve finished.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The minimum surface width is 20 inches.&lt;/p&gt;</string>
    <string name="guardian_draw_desk_body_hands_metric">&lt;p&gt;1. Hold your thumb and index finger on the top front edge of your desk, then pinch and hold both fingers together.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;2. Draw a line from one side of the desk to the other, then open both fingers when you\'ve finished.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The minimum surface width is 50 cm.&lt;/p&gt;</string>
    <string name="guardian_draw_desk_from_workrooms_body_controller_imperial">&lt;p&gt;To use Workrooms, you need to set up a desk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;1. Hold your controller against the front edge of your desk, then press and hold the trigger button.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;2. Draw a line from one side of the desk to the other, then release the trigger button once you\'ve finished.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The minimum surface width is 20 inches.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Press B or Y to cancel.&lt;/p&gt;</string>
    <string name="guardian_draw_desk_from_workrooms_body_controller_metric">&lt;p&gt;To use Workrooms, you need to set up a desk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;1. Hold your controller against the front edge of your desk, then press and hold the trigger button.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;2. Draw a line from one side of the desk to the other, then release the trigger button once you\'ve finished.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The minimum surface width is 50 cm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Press B or Y to cancel.&lt;/p&gt;</string>
    <string name="guardian_draw_desk_from_workrooms_body_hands_imperial">&lt;p&gt;To use Workrooms, you need to set up a desk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;1. Hold your thumb and index finger against the top front edge of your desk, then pinch and hold both fingers together.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;2. Draw a line from one side of the desk to the other, then open both fingers once you\'ve finished.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The minimum surface width is 20 inches.&lt;/p&gt;</string>
    <string name="guardian_draw_desk_from_workrooms_body_hands_metric">&lt;p&gt;To use Workrooms, you need to set up a desk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;1. Hold your thumb and index finger against the top front edge of your desk, then pinch and hold both fingers together.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;2. Draw a line from one side of the desk to the other, then open both fingers once you\'ve finished.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The minimum surface width is 50 cm.&lt;/p&gt;</string>
    <string name="guardian_draw_pt_portal_title">Define Pass-through Area</string>
    <string name="guardian_edit_couch_button">Customise Sofa</string>
    <string name="guardian_edit_desk_button">Customise Desk</string>
    <string name="guardian_edit_whiteboard_button">Customise Whiteboard</string>
    <string name="guardian_existing_couch_body">You already have a sofa in this area. How would you like to modify it?</string>
    <string name="guardian_existing_couch_title">Modify Sofa</string>
    <string name="guardian_existing_pt_portal_body">It looks like you already have a pass-through keyboard area defined. Do you want to modify it?</string>
    <string name="guardian_existing_pt_portal_title">Pass-through Keyboard</string>
    <string name="guardian_existing_whiteboard_body">It looks like you already have a whiteboard in the area. Do you want to modify it?</string>
    <string name="guardian_map_found_with_surfaces">Confirm Playing Area</string>
    <string name="guardian_new_map_desc">Please create a new Guardian boundary for your playing area.</string>
    <string name="guardian_oob_body_in_black">You\'ve left your Guardian boundary. Please remove your headset and return to your playing area, or create a new boundary.</string>
    <string name="guardian_oob_quickboot_body">You\'ve moved too far. Remove your headset and return to your original position, or select Continue if you are in a safe space to continue using your headset.</string>
    <string name="guardian_playspace_clear">Your playing area meets the recommended size. You can use any roomscale, standing or seated experience in this space.</string>
    <string name="guardian_playspace_warning">Redraw your boundary, or lift your headset and remove objects from your playing area. Some objects may not be detected. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Continuing with objects inside or near your boundary may increase your risk of injury or damage. If you get too close to the edge of your playing area, your Guardian boundary will be visible in VR to alert you.</string>
    <string name="guardian_playspace_warning_title">Check for Objects in Playing Area</string>
    <string name="guardian_pt_warning_body">You\'ve spent too long outside a known play area. Please remove your headset or return to your play area.</string>
    <string name="guardian_pt_warning_setup_body">You\'ve spent too long in Guardian setup. Please finish creating a boundary or remove your headset. Visit support.oculus.com for more information.</string>
    <string name="guardian_roomscale_complete_body">Look around to check that this boundary is correctly positioned and clear of any obstructions, including anything you could hit with your arms outstretched.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;These can be used for all sitting or standing experiences. If you get too close to the edge of your playing area, your Guardian boundary will be visible in your VR experience to alert you.</string>
    <string name="guardian_roomscale_complete_playspace_warning_body">Redraw your boundary, or lift your headset and remove objects from your playing area. Some objects may not be detected. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Continuing with objects inside or near your boundary may increase your risk of injury or damage. If you get too close to the edge of your playing area, your Guardian boundary will be visible in your VR experience to alert you.</string>
    <string name="guardian_roomscale_confirm_body_imperial">Your play area meets the recommended size of 6.5 x 6.5 ft or greater. You can use any roomscale, standing or seated experience in this space.</string>
    <string name="guardian_roomscale_confirm_body_metric">Your play area meets the recommended size of 2 x 2 m or greater. You can use any roomscale, standing or seated experience in this space.</string>
    <string name="guardian_roomscale_small_complete_body">Look around to check that this boundary is correctly positioned and clear of any obstructions, including anything you could hit with your arms outstretched.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;These can be used for all sitting or standing experiences. If you get too close to the edge of your playing area, your Guardian boundary will be visible in your VR experience to alert you.</string>
    <string name="guardian_select_couch_button">Sofa</string>
    <string name="guardian_setup_confirm_floor_body">Look down at the virtual grid. If it appears to be at floor level, select &lt;b&gt;Confirm&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;If not, select &lt;b&gt;Reset&lt;/b&gt;. Move the grid down by gently touching the floor with your controller before confirming.</string>
    <string name="guardian_setup_confirm_floor_body_hand">Look down at the virtual grid. If it appears to be at floor level, select &lt;b&gt;Confirm&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;If not, select &lt;b&gt;Reset&lt;/b&gt;. Move the grid down by gently touching the floor with your hand before confirming.</string>
    <string name="guardian_setup_failed_body_imperial">Your playing area is less than the minimum required size of 3 x 3 ft. You can clear more space and redraw your playing area or continue with a boundary for sitting or standing experiences only.</string>
    <string name="guardian_setup_failed_body_metric">Your playing area is less than the minimum required size of 1 x 1 m. You can clear more space and redraw your playing area or continue with a boundary for sitting or standing experiences only.</string>
    <string name="guardian_setup_forward_title">Set Forwards Direction</string>
    <string name="guardian_setup_not_optimal_imperial">Your play area is less than the recommended size of 6.5 x 6.5 ft. You can clear more space and redraw your play area or continue with what you have.</string>
    <string name="guardian_setup_not_optimal_metric">Your play area is less than the recommended size of 2 x 2 m. You can clear more space and redraw your play area or continue with what you have.</string>
    <string name="guardian_stationary_complete_body">Look around to check that this boundary is clear of obstructions, including anything you could hit with your arms outstretched.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This stationary Guardian is for sitting or standing experiences only. If you get too close to the edge of your playing area, your Guardian boundary will be visible in your VR experience to alert you.</string>
    <string name="guardian_stationary_v2_complete_body">Look around to check that this boundary is clear of obstructions, including anything you could hit with your arms outstretched.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This stationary Guardian is for sitting or standing experiences only. When your headset gets close to the edge of your playing area, Pass-through will fade in and you\'ll see a real-time view of your physical environment.</string>
    <string name="guardian_switch_space_couch_body">Confirm sofa as your active playing area or go back to your previous playing area.</string>
    <string name="guardian_switch_space_couch_title">Switch to Sofa</string>
    <string name="guardian_switch_space_desk_body">Confirm desk as your active playing area or go back to your previous playing area.</string>
    <string name="guardian_switch_space_desk_quit_app_body">Confirm desk as your active playing area, or go back to your previous playing area. If you switch to desk now, the app will close and you may lose any unsaved progress.</string>
    <string name="guardian_switch_space_quit_app_button">Quit and Continue</string>
    <string name="guardian_switch_space_roomscale_body">Confirm roomscale as your active playing area or go back to your previous playing area.</string>
    <string name="guardian_switch_space_stationary_body">Confirm stationary as your active playing area or go back to your previous playing area.</string>
    <string name="guardian_tracking_bad_texture_continue">Your playing area lacks the contrast, colour or pattern needed for headset tracking. Please change your playing area to restore tracking.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Guardian is disabled when tracking is off, and you won\'t be alerted to your playing area boundary. If you choose to continue without tracking, use a fixed standing or seated position to avoid injury or damage.</string>
    <string name="guardian_tracking_bad_texture_quit">Your playing area lacks the contrast, colour or pattern needed for headset tracking. Please change your playing area to restore tracking, or exit this app to continue with tracking off.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Guardian is disabled when tracking is off, and you won\'t be alerted to your playing area boundary. Use a fixed standing or seated position to avoid injury or damage.</string>
    <string name="guardian_tracking_lost_body_continue">Something went wrong and your device can\'t track its movement or position in your playing area.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Guardian is disabled when tracking is off, and you won\'t be alerted to your playing area boundary. If you choose to continue without tracking, use a fixed standing or seated position to avoid injury or damage.</string>
    <string name="guardian_tracking_lost_quit">Something went wrong and your device can\'t track its movement or position in your playing area. Please exit this app to continue with tracking off.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Guardian is disabled when tracking is off, and you won\'t be alerted to your playing area boundary. Use a fixed standing or seated position to avoid injury or damage.</string>
    <string name="guardian_tracking_too_bright_continue">It\'s too bright in your playing area to track your headset movement. Please adjust your lighting to restore tracking.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Guardian is disabled when tracking is off, and you won\'t be alerted to your playing area boundary. If you choose to continue without tracking, use a fixed standing or seated position to avoid injury or damage.</string>
    <string name="guardian_tracking_too_bright_quit">It\'s too bright in your playing area to track your headset movement. Please adjust your lighting to restore tracking, or exit this app to continue with tracking off.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Guardian is disabled when tracking is off, and you won\'t be alerted to your playing area boundary. Use a fixed standing or seated position to avoid injury or damage.</string>
    <string name="guardian_tracking_too_dark_continue">It\'s too dark in your playing area to track your headset movement. Please adjust your lighting to restore tracking.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Guardian is disabled when tracking is off, and you won\'t be alerted to your playing area boundary. If you choose to continue without tracking, use a fixed standing or seated position to avoid injury or damage.</string>
    <string name="guardian_tracking_too_dark_quit">It\'s too dark in your playing area to track your headset movement. Please adjust your lighting to restore tracking, or quit this app to continue with tracking off.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Guardian is disabled when tracking is off, and you won\'t be alerted to your playing area boundary. Use a fixed standing or seated position to avoid injury or damage.</string>
    <string name="guardian_welcome_body">Guardian helps you stay within your playing area by creating a boundary around you in VR. This virtual boundary is only visible if you\'re near or touching it.</string>
    <string name="guardian_welcome_body_hand">Guardian helps you stay within your playing area by creating a boundary around you in VR. This virtual boundary is only visible if you\'re near or touching it.</string>
    <string name="launch_check_app_update_dialog_description">%1$s has available updates. Do you want to update now?</string>
    <string name="launch_check_block_desk_dialog_description">This app can\'t be used with desk. To open this app, move to a different playspace and open the app again.</string>
    <string name="launch_check_non_compliant_dialog_description">&lt;p&gt;This app doesn\'t comply with one or more of our policies. You can still use this app, but some functionality may be disabled until the app is in compliance. &lt;a href=\"https://developer.oculus.com/duc-learn-more/\"&gt;Learn More&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</string>
    <string name="launch_check_requires_avatar_dialog_description">You\'re launching an app which uses your Oculus avatar, but it looks like you haven\'t customised an avatar yet. Personalising your avatar will help people recognise you in the app.</string>
    <string name="launch_check_requires_exclusive_microphone_dialog_description">The app you\'re trying to open needs to reserve your microphone. You\'ll remain in this party, but you won\'t be able to hear or talk to your friends until you exit this app.</string>
    <string name="notification_storage_critical_description">The device storage is critically low. You have less than 500 MB remaining.</string>
    <string name="notification_storage_low_description">The device storage is getting low. You have less than 2 GB remaining.</string>
    <string name="passthrough_quickboot_enabled_body">When full Pass-through is enabled, you won\'t need to use a Guardian boundary unless you enter an immersive experience. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Use the Pass-through slider in quick settings to adjust your home environment from full VR to full Pass-through at any time. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For your safety, stay close to your original seated or standing position when Guardian is not active. Keep your playing area clear to prevent injury and follow all instructions and warnings provided on screen and with the headset.</string>
    <string name="passthrough_quickboot_enabled_title">Full Pass-through is On</string>
    <string name="pt_ondemand_nux_body">Double-tap the left or right-hand side of your headset to turn on pass-through at any time. Double-tap again to exit pass-through and get back into VR.</string>
    <string name="pt_ondemand_nux_title">Pass-through Shortcut</string>
    <string name="screenshot_shortcut_body">Press and hold the Oculus button, then press a trigger. Your photos will appear in your camera roll.</string>
    <string name="status_bar_notification_info_overflow">999+</string>
    <string name="toast_passthrough_ondemand_intro">Double-tap the left or right side of your headset to turn off pass-through</string>
    <string name="toast_selected_environment_changed_body">You can change your virtual home environment and choose from a variety of options at any time in Settings.</string>
    <string name="tracking_mode_3dof_incompat_desc">You\'re currently using an app that requires tracking. Turning off tracking will exit this app.</string>
    <string name="tracking_mode_3dof_incompat_title">Exit Open App</string>
    <string name="tracking_off_desc">Guardian is disabled when tracking is off. Turn tracking on to set a Guardian boundary.</string>
    <string name="unofficial_app_body">&lt;p&gt;Our &lt;a href=\"https://developer.oculus.com/distribute/publish-content-guidelines/\"&gt;Platform Abuse Policy&lt;/a&gt; prohibits piracy, illicit modding, cheating and other unauthorised usage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If this unofficial version of &lt;b&gt;%1$s&lt;/b&gt; is not for development purposes, please restore the app to the Oculus Store version now.&lt;/p&gt;</string>
</resources>
